Finding aid for Bentley Historical Library records, 1919 - 2014
Bentley Historical Library
- Administrative Records, 1935-2013; 25 linear feet
  - Terrence J. McDonald (2013-)
    - Conferences and Events
      - Aeon Symposium, 2016
        - Friday Keynote--Kate Hutchens and Moira Fitzgerald
          But what's next? What can/should we be doing with this data? How can, or should, it influence our approaches to not only conflicting priorities and complexities in our service operations, but also security, cataloging, collection development, assessment, and outreach? How do professional concerns around privacy,preservation, and staffing resist such influence, and where might it be appropriate to push on these concerns? How has the advent of "unmediated" requesting changed our relationships with our users? We aim in this session to explore how the area of special collections public services is evolving, and to question how Aeon and similar systems serve us in meeting the changing needs of our remote and onsite patrons.
          Speakers: Kate Hutchens, Special Collections Library, University of Michigan and Moira Fitzgerald, Yale University Library.
        - Thursday Keynote--Christian Dupont
          (Keynote address by Christian Dupont, John J. Burns Library, Boston College)
  - William Wallach, Associate Director
    - Topical
      - Americans with Disabilities Act, 1992-1993 (Box 61)
      - Annotated chronology of University of Michigan events, 1986 (Box 61)
      - Arts of Citizenship Broadway Bridge Project, 1997-2000 (Box 61)
      - Audit, 2006 (Box 61)
      - Building reference manual: BHL Building No. 439 (Energy Star Report), 2000 (Box 61)
      - Collection analysis, 1985-1986 (Box 61)
      - Collection development policies, 1989 (Box 61)
      - Collection development policies, 2006 (Box 61)
      - Computer support cooperative with Center for the Education of Women, 2004 (Box 61)
      - Core work responsibilities and priorities, 2002 (Box 61)
      - Exhibits, 1989-1998 (Box 61)
      - Freedom of Information Act Officers, 1984 (Box 61)
      - Fumigator, 1988 (Box 61)
      - Institute for Museum and Library Studies (IMLS) Grant for Encoded Archival Description (EAD) Development, 1998-2001; 2 folders (Box 61)
      - Masters of forms, undated, circa 1985 (Box 61)
      - Meridian Circle Telescope and Dome Repair, 2010 (Box 61)
      - Michigan Newspapers Project, 1978-1998 (Box 61)
      - MIRLYN cost estimates, 1992-1998 (Box 61)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEA) (Box 61)
        - Enhancing Access to North American Archeological Collections, 2002 (Box 61)
        - Research Fellowship Program for Study of Modern Archives, 1986-1993 (Box 61)
        - Philippine-American Relations at the Turn of the Century: A Scholarly Digital Repository, 1999 (Box 61)
      - National Historical Publications and Records Commission (NHPRC) (Box 61)
        - Appraisal System for Modern Documentation, 1986-1990; 2 folders (Box 61)
        - The Archival Implications of Electronic Communications, 1989 (Box 61)
        - The Impact of Electronic Communications on the Historical Record, 1989 (Box 61)
        - Sienna Heights College Consulting, 1995-1996 (Box 61)
        - The Uses of Electronic Communication to Document and Academic Community, 1990 (Box 61)
      - Parking, 1989 (Box 61)
      - Penn Central Records, 1991 (Box 61)
      - Preservation microfilming, 1989-1991 (Box 61)
      - President's house inventory, 1980-1989 (Box 61)
      - Registration of Copyrights in Bentley Publications, 1974-1978 (Box 61)
      - Report on Rare Books and Special Collections at the University of Michigan (John Dann), 1996 (Box 62)
      - Research Libraries Group (RLG): Archives Preservation Microfilming Project, 1990-1994 (Box 62)
      - Research Libraries Information Network (RLIN), 1982-1993 (Box 62)
      - Research paper topics, 1989 (Box 62)
      - Responses to survey requests, 1979-2004; 3 folders (Box 62)
      - Scene Savers/PPS Group Film Digitization Project, 2010 (Box 62)
      - School of Information and Library Science (SILS), 1987-1991 (Box 62)
      - Staff orientation procedure, 1989 (Box 62)
      - Statistics comparing Bentley to the Clements and Special Collections, 2008 (Box 62)
      - Thompson Gale Microfilm Agreement, 1991-2007 (Box 62)
      - Tour guidelines, 1985; undated (Box 62)
      - Toxic waste site issue, 1994 (Box 62)
      - University Library (ASIS, Vernon Tate and Power Collections), 1983-1989 (Box 62)
      - University of Michigan Extension Service Courses, 1958-1976 (Box 62)
      - Voluntary support report, 2010 (Box 62)
      - Yakel: Curating the Next Generation Finding Aid 2.0, 2006 (Box 62)
      - Zarko, Chet, 1996-2003 (Box 62)
    - Building Addition
      - Architecture Interior Design Planning, 2002 (Box 62)
      - Barrier Free Design Exception, 2001 (Box 62)
      - Building Program, 2002 (Box 62)
      - Design Development Manual, undated (Box 62)
      - Facility condition analysis, 2000 (Box 62)
      - Fire protection: Stack areas, undated; 2 folders (Box 62)
      - Furniture / kitchen estimates, 2001-2004 (Box 62)
      - Infrastructure assessment, 1998 (Box 62)
      - Infrastructure upgrade analysis, 2001 (Box 62)
      - Meetings and memos, 2001-2004; 4 folders (Box 62)
      - Miscellaneous drawings and project manual, 2001-2004 (Box 63)
      - Project Manual, 2002 (Box 63)
      - Shelving shop drawings, 2003 (Box 63)
      - South Stack Shelving Fit Out, 2004 (Box 63)
      - South Stacks, 2004 (Box 63)
      - Design Development Review, 2002 (Box 50)
  - Meetings
    - Administrative Committee of the Bentley Historical Library, 1989-2012 (Box 63)
      - Minutes and agendas, 1989-2012; 2 folders (Box 63)
    - Staff meetings of the Bentley Historical Library, 1972-2008; 0.3 linear feet (Box 63)
      - Minutes and agendas, 1972-2008; 10 folders (Box 63)
  - Historical Society of Michigan
    - Annual meeting, 1959 (Box 64)
    - Constitution, 1935-1967 (Box 64)
    - Correspondence, 1935-1979; 15 folders (Box 64)
    - Financial reports, 1955-1957 (Box 64)
    - Financials, 1956-1959 (Box 64)
    - General, brochures, miscellaneous, 1947-1966 (Box 64)
    - Historical Development Committee, 1958-1959 (Box 64)
    - Museums Conference, 1959 (Box 64)
    - Northern Michigan Historical Conference, 1958-1959 (Box 64)
    - School Activities Council, 1959 (Box 64)
  - Non-Donor Correspondence, 1935-2005
    The next series in the Administrative Records subgroup is the Non-Donor Correspondence (10 linear feet), which is arranged in three alphabetical accessions, each of which covers a period of time. This series contains several kinds of correspondence: there are letters to and from individuals who eventually become donors and financial contributors, as well as letters seeking publication permissions. Most notably, there is professional correspondence between archivists: letters exchanged between leading archivists and Lewis Vander Velde in the 1930s and 1940s, Robert Warner during the late 1960s and 1970s and by Francis X. Blouin in the 1980s and 1990. Taken as a whole, this correspondence demonstrates the growing international influence of the Bentley. Until 1987, the Non-Donor Correspondence included some reference inquiries, after 1987, these records were maintained separately by the Reference Archivist. There is also a folder compiling twenty-five years of thank you notes from various colleagues and professionals from around the country.
    - 1935-1968
      - A-Ho, 1935-1967; 29 folders (Box 16)
      - Audit Reports, 1959; 1963 (Box 16)
      - Automotive Industry Men, 1960 (Box 16)
      - Book Dealer Forest Sweet, 1936-1959 (Box 16)
      - Churches, 1940-1941
        - Baptist Church, 1940-1957 (Box 16)
        - Congregational Church, 1938-1947 (Box 16)
        - Evangelical Lutheran Church, 1939-1940 (Box 16)
        - Presbyterian Church, 1939-1957 (Box 16)
      - Cook, Arthur O., 1935-1940 (Box 16)
      - Couzens, Frank, 1939-1940 (Box 16)
      - Dunlop, Rose (Mrs. Robert), 1953-1958 (Box 16)
      - Galloway, Clyne E., 1939-1946 (Box 16)
      - Gray, Gordon, 1957-1958 (Box 16)
      - Historical Records Survey Publications, 1943 (Box 16)
      - Historical Societies and Collections--Michigan, 1935-1959 (Box 16)
      - [Historical Society of Michigan (Box 64)
      - Hoover, Herbert, 1958 (Box 17)
      - Hoo-M, 1935-1967; 6 folders (Box 17)
      - Maumee Valley International Historical Convention, 1940 (Box 17)
      - Michigan Association and Business Organizations, 1946 (Box 17)
      - Michigan Historical Collections
        - Archival Procedures Conference, 1960 (Box 17)
        - Dr. Bald's Party, 1967 (Box 17)
        - Party of Dr. Vander Velde, 1961 (Box 17)
      - Michigan Historical Commission,1935-1968, 9 folders (Box 17)
        (Lewis Beeson, CJ Sherman)
      - Michigan-Ontario Historical Conference, 1938 (Box 18)
      - N-R, 1935-1967; 7 folders (Box 18)
      - Phelps, Oliver, 1940-1959 (Box 18)
      - Rather, Joseph, 1947-1949 (Box 18)
      - Rau, Louise, 1949-1958 (Box 18)
      - Regents Picture, 1935 (Box 18)
      - Richard, Gabriel, 1934-1939 (Box 18)
      - Robertson, WW (Mrs.), 1948-1949 (Box 18)
      - Ruthven, AG (President of the University of Michigan), 1935-1946 (Box 18)
      - Society of American Archivists (SAA), 1936-1971; 4 folders (Box 18)
        (Waldo G. Leland, Philip C. Brooks)
      - SAA-College and University Archives, 1963-1968 (Box 18)
      - Staff
        - Adams, Elizabeth, 1935-1944 (Box 18)
        - Brown, Henry D., 1937-1946 (Box 18)
        - Chase, Elizabeth Howard, 1940-1947 (Box 18)
        - King, Dorothy, 1944-1947 (Box 18)
        - Vander Velde, LG, 1936-1946 (Box 18)
      - Ta-Tz, 1935-1967 (Box 18)
      - University of Michigan
        - Business Office, 1948-1961 (Box 18)
        - Founders Plaque Conference, 1955 (Box 18)
        - General, 1948-1963 (Box 18)
        - Library Advisory Committee, 1956-1961 (Box 18)
        - "Library Notes,", 1954-1957 (Box 18)
        - Offices A-G, 1948-1960 (Box 18)
        - Offices H-Z, 1947-1967 (Box 18)
        - Summer Sessions, 1955 (Box 18)
      - V, 1938-1946 (Box 18)
      - Vandenburg, Arthur, 1939-1961 (Box 18)
      - W, 1935-1967 (Box 18)
      - Wayne County Treasury, 1949-1955 (Box 18)
    - 1961-1987, 1968-1987
      - A Miscellaneous, 1974-1987; 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Abernathy, Cathy, 1974-1977 (Box 19)
      - Albion College, 1970-1977 (Box 19)
      - B Miscellaneous, 1974-1987; 4 folders (Box 19)
      - Babbage Institute, 1980-1981 (Box 19)
      - Belcher, Louis, 1978 (Box 19)
      - Berkeley, Edmund Jr., 1971-1978 (Box 19)
      - Berner, Richard, 1974-1982 (Box 19)
      - Bicentennial, 1973-1976 (Box 19)
      - Billington, Ray, 1961-1973 (Box 19)
      - Brichford, Maynard, 1972-1982 (Box 19)
      - C Miscellaneous, 1972-1987; 3 folders (Box 19)
      - Charismatic Renewal Services, 1976-1977 (Box 19)
      - Clubb, Jerome M., 1972-1978 (Box 19)
        (see also Machine Readable Archives, Box 2)
      - D Miscellaneous, 1979-1987; 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Dirksen Center, 1977-1978 (Box 19)
      - Doolen, Richard, 1977-1981 (Box 19)
      - Duckett, Kenneth W., 1972-1975 (Box 19)
      - E Miscellaneous, 1986-1987; 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Edwards, John Carver, 1975 (Box 19)
      - Eggert, Gerald G., 1973-1975 (Box 19)
      - Esch, Marvin L., 1969-1976 (Box 19)
      - Evans, Frank, 1978-1979 (Box 19)
      - F Miscellaneous, 1979-1987; 3 folders (Box 19)
      - Fulton, Douglas, 1973 (Box 19)
      - G Miscellaneous, 1979-1987; 3 folders (Box 19)
      - Gillette, John W., 1968-1978 (Box 19)
      - Greenhills School, 1973-1978 (Box 19)
      - Gressley, Gene, 1976-1979 (Box 19)
      - H Miscellaneous, 1973-1987; 3 folders (Box 19)
      - Harmon, Tom, 1973-1982 (Box 19)
      - Helmuth, Ruth, 1972-1978 (Box 19)
      - Herman Miller, Inc., 1986 (Box 19)
      - Historical Society of Michigan, 1968 (Box 19)
      - I Miscellaneous, 1978-1988 (Box 19)
      - Indiana Historical Project, 1973-1975 (Box 19)
      - J Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 19)
      - Jickling, Lyman & Powell, Inc., 1971-1975 (Box 19)
      - Journal of American History, 1976 (Box 19)
      - K Miscellaneous, 1981-1987; 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Koucky, Judy, 1971-1977 (Box 19)
      - L Miscellaneous, 1979-1987; 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Little Traverse Regional Historical Society, Inc., 1961-1975 (Box 20)
      - Lockridge, Ken, 1975 (Box 20)
      - M Miscellaneous, 1973-1987; 4 folders (Box 20)
      - MacCarthy, Alan W., 1973-1977 (Box 20)
      - Michigan Historical Collections
        - Budget, 1968-1975 (Box 20)
        - Building, 1868-1971 (Box 20)
        - Guide to Collections, 1973 (Box 20)
        - Osborne, Mrs. Chase S., 1969-1974 (Box 20)
        - Parsons, Donald, 1967-1970 (Box 20)
        - University of Michigan President's Papers, 1971-1972 (Box 20)
        - Storage and Space, 1970-1971 (Box 20)
        - Tuomy House, 1967-1968 (Box 20)
        - Willow Run, 1967 (Box 20)
      - Michigan Library Association, 1974-1976 (Box 20)
      - Michigan Newspapers on Microfilm (Box 20)
      - Michigan Reader, 1972-1974 (Box 20)
      - Mott, Charles S., 1957-1972 (Box 20)
      - N Miscellaneous, 1977-1987 (Box 20)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1977 (Box 20)
      - O Miscellaneous, 1979-1987 (Box 20)
      - P Miscellaneous, 1975-1987; 2 folders (Box 20)
      - R Miscellaneous, 1979-1987; 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Rhoads, James B., 1970-1979 (Box 20)
      - Richardson, John Jr., 1977-1978 (Box 20)
      - S Miscellaneous, 1973-1987; 4 folders (Box 20)
      - Senior University Officials, 1969-1970; 1973-1980; 1984; 11 folders (Box 20)
      - Society of American Archivists (SAA)
        - General, 1968-1971; 3 folders (Box 20)
          (3 of 4 folders)
        - General, 1968-1971 (Box 21)
          (4 of 4 folders)
        - Burke, Frank, 1967-1968 (Box 21)
        - Cocks, J. Fraser, 1970-1973 (Box 21)
        - Eckles, Robert, 1967-1968 (Box 21)
        - Evans, Frank, 1967-1968 (Box 21)
        - Finch, Herbert, 1965-1969 (Box 21)
        - Grant, 1969 (Box 21)
        - Ham, Gerald, 1967-1969 (Box 21)
        - Kantor, JRK, 1968 (Box 21)
        - Lovett, Robert, 1968 (Box 21)
        - Nelson, Clark, 1968 (Box 21)
        - Questionnaire, 1969-1971 (Box 21)
        - Reports to American Archivist, 1968 (Box 21)
        - Ridge, Alan, 1968 (Box 21)
        - Sueflow, August, 1968 (Box 21)
        - Workshops, 1968 (Box 21)
      - Stewart, William, 1977-1978 (Box 21)
      - Strahan, Frank, 1973-1979 (Box 21)
      - Sturgis, William, 1971-1978 (Box 21)
      - T Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 21)
      - V Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 21)
      - Vecoli, Rudolph G., 1973-1979 (Box 21)
      - Voelker, John, 1958-1974 (Box 21)
      - W Miscellaneous, 1973-1987; 4 folders (Box 21)
      - Warner, Robert, Modern Manuscript Library, 1963-1969 (Box 21)
      - Y-Z Miscellaneous, 1984-1987 (Box 21)
    - 1982-2005, 1988-2000
      - American Friends of the Vatican Library, 1989-2000 (Box 21)
      - Archives Curriculum, 1976-1997; 3 folders (Box 21)
      - Cheever/Knott: Pleasant Walks and Drives, 1998-1999 (Box 21)
      - China Seminar (Joint Seminar on Archival Methods, State Archives Administration of China)
        - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 21)
        - Housing, 1998-1999 (Box 21)
        - Schedule and presentations
          - 1999 (Box 21)
          - 2004 (Box 21)
        - Participants, 1998-2004
          - 1998-1999 (Box 21)
          - 2001, 2004; .ZIP file
          - 2004 (Box 21)
            - Chineses Delegates and Bentley Staff Photographs
            - Photographs
            - Final Reports
      - Committee on the Use of the University Name, 1997; 2 folders (Box 22)
      - Father Gabriel Richard Journals Project, 1999 (Box 22)
      - Ford Library Joint Project, 1982-2000 (Box 22)
      - Hill, Kenneth: CS Smith Bulletin, 1984-1986 (Box 22)
      - Historic Instruments Survey, 1987 (Box 22)
      - Historical Center for the Health Sciences, 1987-1996
        - Minutes and correspondence, 1987-1996 (Box 22)
        - Prospectus, 1989-1990 (Box 22)
      - History and Traditions Committee, 1991-2002
        - Agendas and minutes, 1991-1994; 1998-2002; 2 folders (Box 22)
        - Correspondence, 1994-2000; 2 folders (Box 22)
        - Frost House, 1999-2001 (Box 22)
        - Matthew Zacharias Video, 1992-1993 (Box 22)
        - Native American Plaque, 1999-2002 (Box 22)
        - Plaques, 1998-2000 (Box 22)
        - Steneck/Peckham Book, 1992-1994 (Box 22)
        - Treutner Book, 2000 (Box 22)
      - Hoover Project (Enhancing Access to Russian Archives), 1996 (Box 22)
      - International Council on Archives (ICA), 1986-1997 (Box 22)
      - ICA Maastricht Conference, 1991 (Box 22)
      - ICA: Professional Training and Education Committee, 1985-1991 (Box 22)
      - ICA: Zurich, 1992-1993 (Box 22)
      - International Project, 1984-1995
        - Archives of France, 1984-1995 (Box 22)
        - Blouin/Bearman Conference, 1991 (Box 22)
        - Other (Box 22)
      - Leroy, Aubin Institute national du patrimoine, 2006 (Box 23)
      - Michigan Archival Association (MAA) Legislative Committee, 1990-1993 (Box 23)
      - Midwest Archives Conference (MAC) in Ann Arbor, 1995 (Box 23)
      - MHC Possible Gift Projects, undated (Box 23)
      - Museum Practice Program Executive Committee, 1982-2000 (Box 23)
      - MyStory Project, 1997 (Box 23)
      - National Historical Publications and Records Commission (NHPRC), 1982-1997
        - Administrative Fellow, 1997 (Box 23)
        - Archival Description and Reference for Electronic Conferences Proposal, 1992 (Box 23)
        - Electronic Communications Proposal, 1990-1993 (Box 23)
        - Institute for Advanced Management Proposal, 1982-1986 (Box 23)
        - Invitational Electronic Records Conference Proposal, 1995-1997 (Box 23)
      - Preservation (Box 23)
      - President's Reports, 1986-1988 (Box 23)
      - Regent's History, undated (Box 23)
      - RLIN Project/Catalog Conversion, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
      - Sloan Museum Grant, 1984 (Box 23)
      - Society of American Archivists (SAA), 1984-1995
        - Automated Records and Techniques Taskforce, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
        - Ethics Committee, 1995 (Box 23)
        - Finance Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 23)
        - General, 1992-2000 (Box 23)
      - Staff retreats, 1977-1990 (Box 23)
      - Steneck, Nick, 1984-1986 (Box 23)
      - Visual Resources Project, 1999 (Box 23)
      - Zhimin, Ding, 1989-1990 (Box 23)
    - Non Donor Correspondence, 1982-1995
      - A-C, 1982-1995; 7 folders (Box 23)
      - Currier, Frederick P., 1991-1993 (Box 23)
      - D-G, 1988-1995; 5 folders (Box 24)
      - H-T, 1988-1995; 19 folders (Box 24)
      - Thompson, Benjamin, 1989 (Box 24)
      - Tropman, John, 1991-1992 (Box 24)
      - U-Z, 1988-1995; 4 folders (Box 24)
      - University of Michigan Units, 1988-1995 (Box 24)
      - Non Donor Files A-Z, 1996-2001; 146 files (Box 25)
      - Thank You Notes, 1980-2005 (Box 25)
- Division Records
  The Division Records subgroup (16 linear feet) contains records from the four division units at the Bentley Library: Access and Reference Services, Michigan Historical Collections, Preservation and Conservation, and University Archives and Records Program (UARP).
  - Access and Reference Services, 1961-2000
    The Access and Reference Services, series 1961-2000 (3 linear feet) is broken down into Reference Archivist's files and Reference Reports. Files of the Reference Archivist are grouped according to the department heads. Mary Jo Pugh, Reference Archivist from 1969 to 1984, was the first Reference Archivist of the library. Her topical files include early policy, reference procedures, staff training, guides, and educational outreach activities. Nancy Bartlett was the Reference Archivist from 1985-1998. These records also emphasize reference policy, procedure, and education. The use of visual and electronic archival materials becomes more apparent. A significant number of files relate to outreach efforts within the community including a long-standing partnership with Eastern Michigan University's history program. Kathy Marquis was the third person to hold the Reference Archivist position, 1998-2002. Her records reflect student research at the library through correspondence and project files. They also contain major university issues during the time period including the affirmative action lawsuit. Reference staff development is also portrayed through the development of manuals and meeting minutes.
    The second subseries in this accession is Reference Reports. The early years of reference are shown through the Work Reports. Research topics, user statistics, sample questions, reproduction requests, and annual studies were carefully documented. The Work Report format split into Monthly Reports and Annual Reports in the mid-1980s although generally contain the same type of information. The reports clearly track reference trends and use through the library's history.
    - Reference Archivist's Office, 1961-2000
      Files of the Reference Archivist are grouped according to the department heads. Mary Jo Pugh, Reference Archivist from 1969 to 1984, was the first Reference Archivist of the library. Her topical files include early policy, reference procedures, staff training, guides, and educational outreach activities. Nancy Bartlett was the Reference Archivist from 1985-1998. These records also emphasize reference policy, procedure, and education. The use of visual and electronic archival materials becomes more apparent. A significant number of files relate to outreach efforts within the community including a long-standing partnership with Eastern Michigan University's history program. Kathy Marquis was the third person to hold the Reference Archivist position, 1998-2002. Her records reflect student research at the library through correspondence and project files. They also contain major university issues during the time period including the affirmative action lawsuit. Reference staff development is also portrayed through the development of manuals and meeting minutes.
      - Mary Jo Pugh (Box 26)
        - Archives Class, Reference Segment, 1977-1981 (Box 26)
        - Bibliographic Instruction, 1972-1976 (Box 26)
        - Bibliographies, Historical and Archival, 1961-1985 (Box 26)
        - Class Introductions, 1975-1984
          - American Culture, 1977-1978 (Box 26)
          - Notes, 1975-1984 (Box 26)
          - Oral History, 1975-1977 (Box 26)
          - Political Science, not dated (Box 26)
          - Women's Studies, 1977-1984 (Box 26)
        - Duplication of Manuscripts, Survey, 1962-1963 (Box 26)
        - Guides to the Use of the Michigan Historical Collections, 1972-2002; 2 folders (Box 26)
        - LS/HIS 600 Administration of Archives, 1983 (Box 26)
        - Microfilm Information, 1971-1978 (Box 26)
        - Original Classification Scheme, 1977 (Box 26)
        - Paging Key, not dated (Box 26)
        - Policies, Procedures, and Forms, circa 1977-1983 (Box 26)
        - Privacy and User Studies, 1979-1982 (Box 26)
        - Reference Manual, circa 1977 (Box 26)
        - Reference Space Plans, 1978-1980 (Box 26)
        - Sample Reference Letters, 1976-1979 (Box 26)
        - Staff Reference Exercise -- Role-playing, not dated (Box 26)
      - Nancy Bartlett
        - Audio-Visual Duplication, 1991 (Box 26)
        - Bentley Projects Retreat, 1997 (Box 26)
        - Best of the Bentley Digital Images Project, 1997-1998 (Box 26)
        - Collection Analysis and Development, 1986 (Box 26)
        - Consultants, 1987 (Box 26)